java a boilerplate driven language designed for writing verbose
java 一种样板驱动的语言，设计用于编写冗长
object-oriented instant legacy code it came into being thanks to a relentless
的面向对象即时遗留代码 它的出现要归功于
hype campaign by sun microsystems in the middle of the dot-com bubble it's kind
sun 微系统在dot-com 泡沫中间的无情炒作它
of like the macaulay culkin of programming languages it was originally
有点像最初的编程语言的 macaulay culkin
invented to create a better tv remote than it officially launched for public
发明了一个比它在 1996 年正式推出供公众使用
use in 1996 and nobody's bothered to update the website ever since regardless
的更好的电视遥控器，从那以后没有人费心更新网站，尽管过去
java has been running on 3 billion devices for the last 25 years most of
25 年 java 已经在 30 亿台设备上运行，其中
which are blu-ray players its motto is right once run everywhere which
大部分是蓝光播放器，它的座右铭是 正确的一次运行，
developers know actually means write once debug everywhere remember the log4j
开发人员知道实际上意味着编写一次，到处调试记住 log4j 的
fiasco you can blame java for that one still java has a great mascot a little
惨败，你可以责怪 java 一个仍然 java 有一个伟大的吉祥物，一个
one-eyed monster named duke and people love to hate it so much that it's
名叫 duke 的小独眼怪物，人们非常讨厌它，以至于它
inspired an entire class of programming languages designed to make java better
激发了一个 整个类的编程语言旨在使 java 更好，
like groovy closure scala and kotlin just to name a few unfortunately though
比如 groovy 闭包 scala 和kotlin 只是举几个不幸的例子
there is no cure java also inspired javascript a language that has taken
h 无药可救 java 也启发了javascript 一种语言，
developers 25 years to make halfway decent and one time java even tried to
开发人员花了 25 年的时间才取得了一半的体面，有一次 java 甚至试图
steal javascript's job with applets on the web luckily applet sucks so bad they
通过 web 上的 applet 窃取 javascript 的工作，幸运的是，applet 太糟糕了，它们
made html css and javascript look like a good abstraction for building uis now
使 html css 和 javascript 看起来像现在构建 uis 的好抽象
when your company adopts java you'll also want to adopt oracle database so
当您的公司采用 java 时，您还希望采用 oracle 数据库，这样
you can spend the next 20 years talking about migrating to postgres while paying
您就可以在接下来的 20 年中谈论迁移到 postgres，同时
an ungodly amount of money that will be directly reinvested into these awesome
支付大量资金，这些资金将直接再投资于这些令人敬畏的
sailing yachts to get started set aside a few days to install the jdk jre and
帆船游艇 开始留出几天时间
jvm on your machine it's also recommended that you have a vertical
在你的机器上安装 jdk jre 和 jvm 还建议你有一个垂直
monitor to read the error logs that are coming now before writing any code say
监视器来阅读现在出现的错误日志，然后再写任何代码
this with me public static void main string args public static void main
和我说这个 public static void mainstring args  public static void main
string args now to say hello world create a class java forces you into
string args now to say hello world创建一个类 java 迫使你进入
object oriented programming which means you'll want to read design patterns
面向对象编程，这意味着你需要阅读 de
cover to cover before you go any further now it's time for your public static
在你继续之前先覆盖到覆盖的符号模式现在是你的公共静态
void main string args and then finally system.out.printline with hello world as
无效主字符串参数的时候了，最后是带有 hello world 的 system.out.printline，正如
you can see we get a lot more boilerplate than something like python
你所看到的，我们得到的样板文件比 python 之类的东西要多得多
which is a feature and definitely not a fundamental design flaw or anything
，这是一个特性 绝对不是一个基本的设计缺陷或任何
you'll want to start by writing one giant bloated class then when your boss
你想要从编写一个巨大的臃肿类开始然后当你的老板
complains break it into a hierarchy of deeply nested subclasses that will make
抱怨时将它分解为深度嵌套的子类的层次结构，这将
it impossible to refactor the next step is to ragequit from your job life is way
使得无法重构下一步是从你的 工作寿命
too short to be coding in java man and with that i think i've lost enough
太短了，无法用 java man 进行编码，因此我认为我已经为一个视频失去了足够多的
subscribers for one video there are only two kinds of languages the ones people
订阅者，只有两种语言，人们抱怨的语言
complain about and the ones nobody uses whether you love it or hate it jabba can
和没人使用的语言，无论你喜欢还是讨厌它 贾巴可以
get stuff done and for that it deserves our respect thanks for watching and i
完成任务，为此值得我们尊重，感谢观看，
will see you in the next one
我们下期再见